hello YouTube world this is video number
20 which makes it Friday and finally
have rain today I finally got some sleep
last night
I feel like a human I'm going today to
get my hair cut I'll be my child's
second haircut and looking through
pictures this morning it's so hard to
pick haircuts I don't I kind of want
really short hair and I also don't know
whether I actually want that because I
also like having long hair but I'm
attracted to people with short hair and
that was never a thing what I liked guys
I've never liked mmm I like short hair
hon guys maybe I should get one where as
being attracted to women and non-binary
people with short hair definitely makes
me think like maybe I'm attracted to
because I want to have it and I do have
more of a non-binary feel but I also
have a fear of having short hair I
remember when I had my brain surgery
what if I'm most irrational I guess it
wasn't really a rational but I felt it
was irrational because I'm someone who
doesn't necessarily care so much about
what I look like one of my biggest
worries was that they were gonna have to
shave my head to do it they don't shave
that much of it it's not that noticeable
when they do it because it grows in
really fast it was just their section
down here when I first got it done and
so no my hair was up in a ponytail which
clearly I liked to have it up there but
from a distance you couldn't tell except
in the first view by the time the
bandage was off had already had enough
hair you couldn't necessarily tell and
that I want it and then also my
meditation cool something right word
meditation equipment I was originally
supposed to do it for an hour a day
between 6 and 7 for a hundred days and
it's definitely altered it's now 30
minutes at any time of day I found
really hard to get up at 6 every day I
was getting more and more exhausted and
although I definitely found an hour
beneficial it's just hard to find an
hour to do it non-stop because that's
when it's beneficial it's like the
second part it's like the last 15
minutes that the most stuff comes
through so I probably will change what
anyway so if I didn't do that I was
supposed to shave my head
and I have done it because I've
meditated every day it just hasn't been
that exact time frame and time quit mint
and so part of me also feels like it's
like partial like shaving my head if I
got my haircut super short and so yeah
so on Monday when I do my video we'll
see what I look like then Thanks